What the hell?
Hey!
You know which side of the border
you're on?
You got a name, boy?
Guess someone must have
cut your tongue off.
Either that, or —
you've got something to hide.
As far as I can tell —
you hear me plain enough!
Heh.
"Walter Henderson."
Now, I want to ask you
one last question.
You see this here card?
Is this you —
or a relative of yours?
Well — I'm going to call up this number,
and see if they can tell me who you are!
I ain't got beds enough
to be puttin' up mutes.
Operator — I need a line out, please.
Uh — What?
What? Can you — can you tell me
the exact location of your hospital, down there?
Where the hell is that?
Oh — okay, alright.
Yeah — okay.
I'll get there as fast as I can.
Just — will you tell him
that I'm coming, okay?
Okay.
Ann, honey?
I just got the strangest phone call.
Who from?
From some hospital in South Texas.
A place called "Terlingua" —
they say they found Travis.
Oh, no.
What are you going to do?
Well, I'll go down and get him.
Oh, wow —
Well, what am I gonna do?
I can't leave him down there.
What about Hunter?
What am I supposed to tell him?
Well, just tell him
I had to go on a business trip.
I mean — about Travis.
I guess you'd better tell him the truth.
10 to Van Horn 90 —
then Alpine 118 South —
Terlingua.
You must be the brother of the mute.
Mute?
Yeah — I couldn't squeeze the
time of day outta him!
Must be in a kind of jam!
I dunno — I haven't seen him
in over four years.
Is that right?
Well, a lot can happen
to a man in four years.
All kinds of trouble —
bits of trouble.
What do you mean?
Well — down here —
a man gets himself into a fix, sometimes.
It costs him a little to get him out —
if you understand what I mean.
I don't understand you.
I wish you get to the point,
because I'd like to see my brother.
Alright, son.
But first —
I would like to ask you something.
Did your brother ever get himself
into a car wreck?
Car wreck — no —
not that I know of.
Then he must be mixing
with some hard company.
I'd like to see my brother now —
If you don't mind.
He disappeared!
You mean — he's not here?
After I came all this way?
He's been gone since
early this morning.
We have his possessions.
Nevertheless — saved them.
We'd be glad to turn him over to you —
soon as you take care of our little reward.
Travis — hey —
Don't you recognize me? It's Walt!
It's your brother — Walt.
What the hell happened to you, anyway?
You look like forty miles of rough road.
Come on — let's get in the car —
Trav?
C'mon.
Here, Trav — here's your stuff.
Got that back at that clinic,
back there.
Sure picked a hell of a spot to land in —
I don't blame you for running out of it.
Look, Trav —
we've got quite a bit of traveling to do here.
You're not gonna clam up
the whole way, are you?
I'm going to get kinda lonely.
Trav?
Would you mind telling me where you disappeared to
or the last four years?
Have you seen Jane — or talked to her?
Ann and I —
we sorta gave up on you — we actually —
we thought you were dead, boy!
This is pretty, uh —
Okay.
Well —
Well, gee, Trav — maybe you wanna —
get cleaned up — take a shower or something?
I think I'll go back into town
and get you some new clothes.
You could use a new
set of clothes, couldn't you?
What size shoes do you wear?
Let's see —
I'm probably one size bigger, huh?
Where'd you find that beard?
Pretty snazzy.
Okay —
I'll zip into town and zip right back.
I won't be gone long.
You'll be okay — won't you, Trav?
Yeah — I'll be right back.
Dammit —
Mind telling me where
you're headed, Trav?
What's out there?
Nothin' out there.
Don't you trust me or something?
I'm just trying to help you, Trav —
that's all.
C'mon — it's alright.
C'mon with me in the car.
Feels good to be in new clothes, huh?
Hi — Hunter?
It's Daddy.
I thought you'd be in bed already!
Guess who I'm visiting
here in Texas.
Your father!
You remember your father?
Not at all?
He was?
Well — guess what?
I'm gonna bring him home to visit.
Travis —
Do you remember your little boy —
Hunter?
Well — he's with us.
He's been living with Ann and me,
ever since you disappeared.
We didn't know what else to do —
so we just kept him.
One day, he was just standing at the door.
All he could tell us was that
someone brought him there in a car.
He didn't know what had happened to you —
or Jane —
so we tried everything we could
think of to find you — or Jane —
tried to locate her — she'd vanished, too.
We didn't know what else to do.
Travis —
I dunno what kind of trouble you got into —
I dunno what happened —
But dammit — I'm your brother, man.
You can talk to me.
I'm tired of doing all the taking.
Fill it with unleaded, please.
You know — I'm getting a little sick
of this silence routine.
You can talk!
I can be silent too, y'know.
I just assume that both of us'll
keep our mouths shut for the whole rest of the trip —
Paris.
What?
Paris?
Did you ever go to Paris?
No?
Could we go there now?
It's a little outta the way.
No, I've never even been to Europe —
Ann keeps on wanting to go there —
well, she's from France — you remember?
But, we never seem to find the time,
'cause my company keeps me kinda busy.
Let's go, Trav.
What's the matter?
Where are we going?
We're gonna fly to L.A.
You're not afraid of flying, are you?
We're — leaving the ground?
Yeah.
Why?
Because it's too far to drive.
It would take an extra two days —
I can't afford the time, Trav.
Why?
It's just easier to fly, Trav.
It's faster. C'mon!
We'll get'cha home, okay?
When I get you home, I'll get you settled,
and then you can do whatever you want!
But, sir — we can't stop the plane
every time someone gets terrified!
Don't get on a plane, and then
refuse to leave the ground!
Don't do things like that!
This isn't the wilderness!
You're living with people, now!
Okay?
You should have acquired a private plane —
do you realize how many people you're detaining?
Sorry!
I'm sorry — I'm sorry — I'm sorry —
okay?
This is getting a little ridiculous, Travis.
Are you going to leave me?
No, I'm not going to leave you.
It's alright if you leave me.
I don't know honey — no —
He just panicked or something.
Well — it won't do any good to try another plane —
it wasn't the plane — he'll just get off again!
Well — we're just gonna
have to drive it — that's all.
Yeah — it'll take a good two days.
I don't understand why you have to
have the very same car you had before!
They're all alike —
all the cars we have here are 'Birds,
Oldses, Chevys, and whatever —
I'm not even sure I can locate the same car
you had before!
I know — my brother left something in the car —
we're hoping we can search the car and find it!
Oh — well, I'll just contact the
Lost and Found Department for you if that's okay, sir —
No — we have to have the very same car.
Well — I can't do that!
There's no way I can trace that car for you.
Well, why not?
You've got the license number right on your form, there!
Well — yes, but —
Well, just give us the license number
and we'll find it!
But I can't allow you on the lot, sir.
Why not? We're already on it!
I just have to ask you
to come back to the office with me.
Travis!
What?
I don't think we're gonna
get the very same car.
But I can rent you a model that's
just like the one you had before, sir.
I need the same car, Walt!
How are we gonna go in another car?
Give us the number — will ya, please?
Come on — pretty please?
Alright — that number is 667 DJP.
Remember that? 667 DJP?
It's got a bump on the hood —
Yes it does.
What's that?
What?
That — what you've got in your hand?
A picture.
A picture of what?
A picture of —
Paris.
Paris — really?
Yes — a picture of a piece of Paris.
Where'd you get a picture of Paris?
Can I see it?
Yes.
This is it?
This is Paris?
Looks just like Texas to me.
It is.
Paris, Texas?
It's right here on the map.
There's really a place called
Paris, Texas?
It's right here!
Well — how come you've got a picture
of a vacant lot in Paris, Texas?
It's mine!
I know that — but how come you got it?
I purchased it — in the mail —
a long time ago.
You bought a picture
of vacant lot in the mail?
No — I bought the land —
Oh, you bought that lot!
Yes.
Lemme see it again.
There's nothing on it!
Empty.
Well — why in hell would you wanna buy
a vacant lot in Paris, Texas, for Christ's sake?
I forgot.
Here, Trav.
Do you remember
what Mama's very first name was?
Mary.
No — I know — I mean her —
before she found Daddy.
Oh — her maiden name?
Yeah.
You don't remember her maiden name?
No.
Zaquine.
Spanish.
Her father was.
Yeah?
I don't believe it!
You finally decided to eat!
Eating and talking!
Before you know it,
you'll be back in the land of the living!
You want me to drive?
Sure! Think you remember how?
My body remembers.
You can sleep while I drive.
Okay.
Well, Trav —
think maybe you're ready to —
tell me what the hell happened to you
over the last four years?
No — not yet.
Travis?
What?
Where are we, Travis?
What happened?
Why'd we get off the highway?
Jesus Christ.
I can't even sleep for five minutes
without some crisis.
Why'd you turn off?
I don't know where I turned off.
Didn't have a name.
That's great.
That's just damn great.
Here we are — in the middle of the Mojave Desert —
in a place that doesn't have a name!
I could find the highway again.
Trav — I need to talk to you a little bit
about Hunter.
How old is he now?
He's eight in January.
He's seven, then.
Yeah.
But, see — what I want to talk about is —
well — he's like part of the family, now.
Ann and me are like his parents now.
Ann's your wife.
Yeah — you remember her, don't you?
No. — does he think that you're his father?
Well — Ann told him you were coming.
Who does he think I am?
I told him you're his father.
But — see —
you've been gone a long time, Trav.
How long have I been gone?
Do you know?
Four years.
Is four years a long time?
It is for a little boy.
That's half his life!
Half a boy's life.
I remember now —
What?
Why I bought that land.
Oh — why?
Well — Mama once told me that, uh —
that's where she and Daddy first —
made love.
Oh — in Paris, Texas?
Yeah.
She told you that?
So — I figured that —
that's where I began.
I mean me — Travis Clay Henderson —
they named me that.
I started out there.
Paris, Texas, huh?
Yeah.
So you think —
maybe you were conceived there?
Yeah.
You could be right, Travis.
Daddy always had a joke about it.
What was the joke?
He would introduce Mama
as the girl he met in Paris.
And then he'd wait —
before he said Texas —
'til everybody thought that he meant —
he would wait before he said Texas,
'til everybody thought —
after everybody thought
that he was talking about Paris, France.
He always laughed real hard about it.
So you live in Los Angeles, huh?
Yeah — well, we live in the suburbs,
but I've got my business in town.
What's your business?
I make billboard signs —
for advertising.
Oh, yeah?
So you're the one that makes all those —
I love those.
Some of 'em are beautiful.
I'm not the only one in the world
that makes 'em, Trav.
Trav? This way.
Nice, huh?
Just been in here three months.
I really like it —
but I took a beating on the financing, I'll tell ya —
like everybody else nowadays,
I guess.
Hi, baby.
Everything okay here?
Oh, sure. We just missed you a lot.
I missed you, too.
Come in!
Travis.
My god.
We were beginning to wonder
if we'd ever see you again.
It's been so long.
Did you have a good trip?
Yeah — it was fine.
Hunter?
Hunter —
this is Travis.
Hi.
I bet it was really hot
coming across the Mojave Desert.
Yes.
Too bad you had to drive.
What happened?
Well — Travis just didn't feel like flying.
Oh — I don't blame you.
I can't stand airplanes anymore.
Especially since we live in this house.
All we hear is planes, day in and day out —
I like them.
You used to fly — didn't you, Travis?
No.
Oh, I thought — I remember Jane
telling me that you once flew to Dallas together — or somewhere.
Maybe I'm mistaken.
Honey — he hasn't slept in a bed
since we started — I swear to God!
I don't think that's even necessary.
Where has he been sleeping, then?
Well — he doesn't sleep!
He has to sleep somewhere.
Okay — but I don't think
he's even going to use it.
He's got to get tired some time!
Oh —
there is a towel for you, Travis —
and some underwear and socks, from Walt.
Goodnight.
Thank you.
Okay. Get some shut-eye.
Okay.
- Sweet dreams.
- Alright.
You polished them!
That's very nice of you, Travis.
Would you like to come in
and have some breakfast?
Aren't you hungry?
We are going to have strawberry waffles!
Do you like them?
Do you want some?
Well — there is hot coffee on the stove,
if you want some.
Look at that truck.
Hi.
Decided to rough it, huh?
Yeah.
What did you do — spit-shine these?
I can get you a job
at the airport doing that.
Hey — do you wanna trade these new boots
for those old boots?
Yeah — you can wear 'em.
Thank you.
Travis? I have to rush off
to get Hunter to school on time.
We will be back this afternoon.
Walt's office number is
on the dining room table.
See you later!
Okay.
Bye!
Ann?
Yeah?
I was just thinking —
maybe I can meet Hunter after school —
and we could walk home together —
if he wants to.
That sounds like a great idea, Travis.
Walk home?
I don't wanna walk home, Mom.
Nobody walks — everybody drives.
Come on, Hunter —
it won't hurt you to walk home once in your life!
No — no —
I don't want to.
Travis, I insist —
he'll wait for you out in front.
Everybody'll see me!
Walt can tell you how to get there —
it's not far —
and get into the car, Hunter —
we are late as it is.
You're mean.
Can I come with you?
Sure.
I'm really sorry about this, Travis.
It's not easy for him, Ann.
Ann, it's okay — he's in here.
What are you doing?
Driving.
Where to?
Just driving.
You're not hiding out in there, are you?
No.
Hunter —
Travis is your real dad —
you know that, don't you?
Dad? When are they gonna
make spaceships like they make cars?
Hunter — I'm asking you a question.
Can you answer it?
What?
Well — Travis went to meet you at school —
and he wanted to walk you home.
Nobody walks.
That's not the point.
Travis is your real dad, and —
he wants to talk you.
Why? What about?
Okay — come on. Let's go have dinner.
Hey, Trav? Do you remember that time
when Ann and me came down to visit you — about five years ago?
No.
You and Jane were down in Texas —
right there on the coast.
Hunter was about three.
Don't you remember that?
No.
I remember — we went fishing.
Yeah.
I took some Super 8 on that trip —
and I put it all together.
Thought maybe you might
like to see some of it.
What is it?
Movies. You know — Super 8?
Oh.
Walt — maybe Travis doesn't want —
What?
Well — maybe he'd like to wait a while
before he looks at it.
Yeah — it's up to him.
Just maybe thought you'd
like to see some of it.
Movies? Sure.
Great! There's some great stuff on it —
some great shots of Hunter in it.
I've already seen it!
Well, you have to see it again.
Come on — help me set up the projector.
Okay.
That's me driving!
I know — you're gonna be good.
Time for bed now, Hunter.
Oh, Mom —
Time to go to bed — it's past ten.
Goodnight, Dad.
Goodnight, baby.
Do you think he still loves her?
How would I know that, Hunter?
I think he does.
How can you tell?
Well — the way he looked at her.
You mean, when he saw her in the movie?
Yeah — but that's not her.
What do you mean?
That's only her in a movie —
a long time ago —
in a galaxy far, far away.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for — uh —
the father.
Your father?
No, no — just a father —
any father.
What does a father look like?
There are many different kinds of fathers,
Señor Travis.
Well — I just need one.
You think you're gonna
find him in there?
Well — I don't know where else to look.
Oh, I see — you want to look like a father.
Yeah.
Tell me — do you want to be a rich father?
Uh — no.
A poor one?
No.
Then, which?
In-between.
No — no — there is no in-between, eh?
You either have to be a rich father
or a poor one.
Rich.
Bueno. Un momento.
Ta bien.
Ahora sí. Okay.
A ver — huh?
¿Qué tal? Eh?
Está bueno.
Okay —
one thing you must remember —
to be a rich father, Señor Travis,
you must look to the sky — and never at the ground.
Little higher.
Eso. Mmm-hmm.
Ahora camina.
No — este —
You must walk stiff,
Señor Travis.
Con confianza — ¿me entiende?
Um — con respeto.
Dignity.
Eso! Con ¡dignidad!
You got it.
Who is that guy — you know him?
Yeah — he's my father's brother.
No — they're both brothers.
No — they're both fathers.
No — ah, forget it.
But both whose fathers?
My father.
How can you have two fathers?
Just lucky, I guess.
Well, bye!
Bye.
That's my dad's suit!
I mean — Walt.
That's okay if you call him "Dad."
Yeah — I borrowed it from him.
He said it was okay.
What are those pictures?
That's my dad —
your grandfather.
What was his name?
Travis.
Same as yours?
Where is he, now?
He died.
Couple of years after this picture —
in that car.
Oh. He's dead?
Mmm-hmm.
But, can you feel that he's dead?
What do you mean?
You knew him
when he was walking around and talking — right?
Yeah.
So can you feel that he's gone?
Yeah — sometimes.
I know he's dead.
I never felt like you were dead.
I could always feel you were walking
around and talking — someplace.
I feel Mom, too.
You do?
Don't you?
Yeah.
That's me — when I was in the Navy.
You were a general?
No! That's was when I was in the band —
the high school band.
Here's you. I like this picture.
Look at that.
That is really wild.
That's weird when it —
when there's water in between — and then it turns into nothing —
and it goes psshhhh.
That's a great picture.
And this is my mom —
your grandmother.
I didn't know.
It just seems that —
everything has changed
between us so fast —
ever since Travis came.
What's changed?
I'm just afraid.
Afraid of Travis?
No.
Then what?
Of what will happen to us if we lose Hunter.
We're not gonna lose Hunter.
Then why do you keep pushing them together?
It's almost as if you wanted him to leave.
Who?
Hunter.
You know what I'm talking about.
You keep promoting this
father-son business between —
It's not "business."
Travis is his father,
and Hunter is his son.
That's a fact.
You've known that all along.
Travis happens to be my brother.
I know he is.
Well — what's this "promotion" bullshit?
You want us to go on pretending —
that we're the parents
of my brother's son?
Well, how long do you expect Hunter
to buy that?
I was never pretending.
I love him — just like
he was my own flesh and blood.
So do I.
Hi, Ann.
Hi, Travis.
You don't sleep much, do you?
Travis.
There is something I have to tell you.
I was not going to —
because somehow it makes things easier
that nobody knows.
I never even told Walt or Hunter.
What is it?
After Hunter came to live with us —
Jane used to call —
asking about him.
She made me promise not to tell anyone
that she was calling.
Did she ask about me?
Yes — in the beginning.
Where did she call from?
Places in Texas.
What places?
Let me finish, Travis.
After what happened
between you and Jane —
she decided Hunter should be with us.
She said she couldn't be a mother to him any more.
She stopped being a mother to him
a long time before that.
Travis. I don't want to feel I'm
hiding something from you anymore.
She was young —
she wanted something —
but I just couldn't figure out what it was.
I just didn't realize how much rage I had.
A little more than a year ago,
she stopped calling.
I haven't heard from her since then.
Nothing?
Not a word.
But on the last call —
she asked for me
to open a bank account for Hunter.
A bank account?
All I know about Jane now, is —
she goes to this bank —
on the fifth of each month —
and wires money for Hunter.
Jane still sends him money.
Sometimes, a hundred dollars —
sometimes, fifty — or five —
for Hunter's future.
I had the bank trace the wire.
It comes from a bank in Houston.
What bank?
I wrote it down — if you want it.
What's the date today?
The first of November.
You will all be caught with your diapers down —
that is a promise!
I make you this promise on my mother's head.
For right here — today —
standing on the very head of my mother —
which is on God's green earth —
which everybody who wasn't born in a fuckin' sewer —
oughta know and understand to the very marrow of their bones.
They will invade you in your beds.
They will snatch you from your hot tubs.
They will pluck you right outta your fancy sports cars.
There is nowhere —
absolutely nowhere —
in this godforsaken valley.
I'm talking about — from the range of my voice, right here —
Clear out to the goddamn Mojave Desert —
and beyond that — clear out past Barstow —
and everywhere else in the Valley —
all the way out to Arizona —
None of that area will be called the Safety Zone.
There will be NO Safety Zone.
I can guarantee you the Safety Zone
will be eliminated —
eradicated!
You will all be extradited to the Land of No Return.
It's a navigation to nowhere!
And if you think that's going to be fun —
you've got another thing coming.
I may be a slimebucket —
But believe me — I know what the hell I'm talking about.
I'm NOT crazy!
And don't say I didn't warn you! I WARNED you!
I warned ALL of you!
Thought you were afraid of heights!
No — I'm not afraid of heights —
I'm afraid of falling.
Oh yeah?
Well — just don't look down.
Too bad things don't look
the same on the ground.
What do you mean?
Things are clearer, up here.
Might clear things up.
Yeah — I had a talk with Ann last night —
yeah — she's pretty upset.
Yeah — I know.
I'm gonna leave.
What?
I'm leaving.
I didn't tell you this in order to make you leave —
I'm not trying to get rid of you, Travis —
I know that.
Well — what good is that gonna do?
That's not gonna solve anything.
I'm gonna find Jane.
How're you gonna do that?
It's been four years.
She's completely disappeared —
I tried to find her — I tried everything —
I couldn't find her.
Well, I haven't tried yet.
I can find her.
What makes you so sure?
I just know.
Can we go down now?
No.
Goddammit —
You tell me what happened,
Travis!
I'm sick of this fuckin' mystery!
I've been treating you like a spoiled kid
ever since I picked you up in the desert!
Now, you tell me what happened
with you and Jane!
Shit.
I know —
it's none of my business.
Uh —
well, I need to take —
money — credit cards —
Alright — sure — you can have 'em.
You know you'll get it back —
Oh — forget that. You can have 'em.
I wanna find her, Walt.
Hunter.
That your car?
Yup! C'mon!
Radical.
This is not bad stuff.
Ann puts it in lunch, every day.
La Vache Qui Rit. Sticky.
La Vache what?
Rit. Rrrr-rrrit.
I like it.
Dad —
Yeah?
Where'd you go,
all that time?
Mexico.
How come?
I didn't know where else to go.
Where'd Mom go?
I don't know.
But right now,
she's somewhere in Houston.
That's where the Space Center is!
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I gotta go away now.
Why?
Because I'm gonna find her.
What about me? You just found me.
Can I come with?
What about Walt and Ann?
You mean, we'd never come back here?
Wel, sure, but —
I dunno when.
I want to come with.
I wanna find her, too.
When do we go?
Right now.
Then c'mon —  let's go.
First, we gotta stop
and get supplies for the trip.
Okay.
We gotta buy jackets — T-shirts —
toothbrushes — stuff like that —
maybe even walkie-talkies!
Talkies — of course!
Just in case!
Do you know what?
What?
This whole galaxy —
the whole universe —
used to be compressed
into a tiny spot — this big.
And — and —
you know what happened?
What?
It went pshhhhh and blew up.
All the spark —
everything went flying all over the place —
and formed space —
it was just gas. It was floating around —
The Earth was?
Yeah — the Earth was really gas.
And — and the Sun formed —
and it was so hot —
that the Earth just formed
into one hard, big ball —
of ocean —
nothing but ocean.
So there was sea animals,
and under the water —
a volcano went pshhhhh —
And —
the hot lava hit the water —
and formed rock — to make land.
You know how to make a collect call?
You dial the operator, and tell her that —
I know.
Good —
then call Walt and Ann.
Why?
Because —
so they don't worry about you —
so they know where you are.
But what am I gonna say?
Just tell 'em the truth.
Tell them that you're with me,
and that we're going to Texas.
They're gonna flip out.
No —
but you can handle it.
Okay?
Why can't you do it?
I can't do it.
Why?
Because it has to be you.
Oh, geez.
Why can't he do anything —
Hello —
Hunter. Where are you?
You know what time it is?
I've been calling everywhere looking for you.
Yeah, yeah —
Hunter — just listen to me, now.
Where are you, exactly?
San Bernadino?
Hunter — what do you mean
you're in San Bernadino?
Wait, honey.
How did —
Let me talk to him.
Hunter.
Are you alright?
What are you doing?
With Travis?
Where are you going?
Tell me where you are Hunter —
just tell me where you are.
What's the name of it?
Oh my god.
Hunter.
You tell Travis to turn around —
And come back here,
right now.
Do you understand me?
Let me talk to him.
What should I do?
Just hang up.
Bye, Mom. Gotta go now!
Hunter —
Hunter!
Did they flip out?
Yeah — she did.
You're not sorry you came,
are you?
No.
Well — you can go back to them
any time you want.
You just tell me, okay?
I don't wanna go back.
Well — I know — but just in case
you change your mind.
I'm so used to calling her "Mom."
Ann?
Yeah.
She sounded so sad.
I know.
What do you think Mom
will look like, now?
I dunno.
Do you remember her?
Not really —
only from that little movie we saw.
You looked happy, then.
Yeah.
You keep that.
Night.
Dad —
if a guy put a baby down —
travelled at the speed of light
for —
If he travelled at the speed of light —
He would come back in an hour —
he would be an hour older —
but the little baby
would be a very old man.
Oh yeah?
Well, how long would it take him
to get to Houston?
Uh — if they were to travel —
I'd say about three seconds.
Uh — over —
I didn't get that last part.
It would take them three seconds
to get from California to Houston —
on light-speed.
This is Houston?
Yup.
How are we gonna find her
in a big city like this?
I know where she'll be.
Where?
A bank. She's gonna deposit
some money at a certain bank today.
This is a bank?
What kind of bank is this?
Looks like a drive-in.
I've never seen a bank like that.
Me neither.
There are so many cars —
we'll never find her.
Oh — yeah, we will.
C'mon.
We will split up — and then
we'll cover more ground — okay?
Yeah — we could use the walkie-talkies.
Hey — now you're going.
I'll let you out here.
Okay.
Can you hear me, Dad?
Over.
Loud and clear.
Good.
Hunter in Position 1.
Over.
Travis in Position 2 —
we got it covered.
I told you it'd be
more than toys. Over.
10-4 — over and out.
Dad —
she's just leaving the bank.
Get over here.
Dad — can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
She's leaving the bank!
Get over here!
Dad!
Come on!
Dad! Wake up!
Wake up! She's leaving!
She's leaving the bank!
Dad! Wake up!
Is she — where —
I'm on my way!
Oh no —
She went that way!
Which way did she go?
That way.
You sure it's her?
C'mon — c'mon — c'mon! Let's go!
Hunter — did you really
get a good look at her, or what?
It was the right one —
I know it was her!
Oh, god — I hope we haven't lost her.
Can this piece of junk go faster?
There's ten thousand cars here, Hunter —
how're we gonna find her?
I dunno — which one is it?
Go faster, Dad! Go faster!
Wh — what colour —
the car was red, right?
Yeah — a little red Chevy.
Do you see anything?
Yeah — I don't which one it looks like, Hunter —
you'll have to help me look —
can you see it?
No — not yet.
I see her — I see her!
Where — where?
Over in that lane — in that lane!
Which — which lane?
The right one!
Alright, alright —
settle down — I see it.
Is that her — look —
see if it's her. Can you tell?
I can't tell.
Wait a minute —
there's two red cars now!
Which one is it?
Uh — the right —
The left one!
You sure?
Yeah, the left one!
Okay.
You're sure this is the one, though —
Yeah!
Okay.
I hope you're right, Hunter.
If we're following the wrong car,
we're gonna have to wait a whole other month.
I'll be eight, then.
You'll be what?
I'll be eight, then!
Let's get closer! We could wave!
No, no, no — we don't wanna get too close —
we might scare her —
she'd have a wreck or something.
Okay?
Okay. I guess so.
Well — I wonder where she's going.
Maybe to work — what do you think?
Yeah — could be.
Looks like a girl's car to me.
Could it be hers?
Could be — get in the truck
and I'll tell you my plan.
Okay.
Roll the windows up, lock the doors,
and if anybody talks to you —
tell them your daddy's inside,
and he'll be right back. Okay?
Okay.
You okay?
Yup.
Sargeant Jojo — call for you — Booth #22.
Sargeant Jojo — Booth #22.)
Okay — new bit — new bit!
You guys are gonna love this!
The girls here spend so much time
with a guy, that most of them live alone.
But it's tough living alone
in a city like this!
A lot of violent things happen here —
stuff like rape — like murder!
（ＴＨＥ ＭＹＤＯＬＬＳ）
(Especially from the police force.)
Uh — Tupperware parties!
Violent things!
And when you live alone,
you gotta think —
"Well, do I need some kind of protection in the home?"
And — for a girl — you can live with a guy —
or you can have a dog —
That's a tough decision,
lemme tell you —
Now — what normal-thinking adult
wants to live with something —
(Nurse Bibbs — you're needed in Booth #7.
Nurse Bibbs — Booth #7.)
that hates to take a bath —
and, uh — that throws up on the carpet —
and chews out your underwear —
Looks like a dog act to me.
Yeah, right.
Dogs, on the other hand, are real cute!
They have cute little noses — cute little tails —
Again?
Lotta sick people out there!
Let's hear some rock 'n' roll —
hey — how's it goin'?
Let's hear you play!
Give us something good!
You're getting better all the time!
(♫ ＴＨＥ ＭＹＤＯＬＬＳ － Ａ ＷＯＲＬＤ ＯＦ ＨＥＲ ＯＷＮ ♫)
Sir?
Sir — you're in the wrong place.
It's too early —
all the girls are downstairs.
Please get it right,
'cause I'm getting — I'm getting crazy.
Mother Dina —
call for you — Booth #19.
Booth #19.
Yeah — who do you want?
Yeah — I wanna see a blond girl
with kinda short, straight hair — about 25 years old.
Okay.
She's coming down —
stay on the line.
Hello, honey.
Oh, mercy.
You know — twenty-three — I've worked
twenty-three of the twenty-four booths in this place —
Poolside made twenty-four.
So — what can I do for you today?
I have an idea —
How about water polo?
Fun.
Um — well —
tell you what —
Why don't you just tell Nurse Bibbs
where the pain is?
Maybe I can find a cure — hmm?
Uh — why don't you look at me?
I am looking at'cha!
Yeah, but I'm over here —
can't you see me?
Listen, sweetheart — if I could see you,
I wouldn't be working here.
Well — what do you see?
I see what you see. Nurse Bibbs.
Nurse Bibbs and a rubber horse.
Oh — oh — I see.
Thank you, Nurse Bibbs.
Thank you.
Hi!
You out there?
Well — I see your light's still on,
so I guess you must be out there.
Hmm?
It's okay if you don't want to talk,
y'know.
I don't wanna talk either, sometimes.
I just like to stay silent.
Do you mind if I sit down?
No.
Thanks.
My legs get a little tired
from standing all the time.
Is this your first visit here?
Yes.
Oh — well, this whole thing must seem
kinda strange to you, huh?
You realize that I can't see you, even
though you can see me.
Well, that takes a little getting used to.
Am I —
am I looking at your face now?
Oh, god, it don't matter.
If, um —
if there's anything you wanna talk about —
I'll just listen.
Alright?
I'm a real good listener.
Is there something —
I dunno —
is there something I can do for ya?
Do you mind if I take off my sweater?
I'll just take off my sweater.
No — no — no.
Don't —
Please —
please leave it on.
I'm sorry.
I just don't know exactly
what it is you want.
I don't want anything.
Oh —
why'd you come here, then?
I wanna talk to you.
Is there something you wanna tell me?
No.
You can tell me —
I can keep a secret.
Is that all you do —
just talk?
Well — yeah.
Yeah — mostly —
— and listen.
What else do you do?
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
So what else do you do?
Nothing, really.
Oh, well — we're not allowed
to see the customers outta here.
Yeah? What if you see them —
do you go home with them?
No sir — we don't.
We're not allowed to have any outside
relationships with the customers.
Yeah, but you can really see them
if you want to — can't you —
I mean, you can go home with them
if you want to — all these places say that.
I mean — how much extra money do you make?
How much money do you make on the side?
I'm sorry, sir.
I think you maybe wanna talk to one of the other girls —
I'll see if I can find one for ya.
No — no — no — no!
Please.
Please don't go.
I just don't think
I'm the one you wanna talk to.
Please.
Please don't go — I'm sorry.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Y'know — I know how hard it is
to talk to strangers, sometimes.
Just relax.
Relax, and tell me
what's on your mind.
I'll listen —
— to you.
I don't mind listening.
I do it all the time.
She was there, wasn't she?
What's that?
A vacant lot.
I bought that land
when we were all together — with your mom.
I thought we might live there, someday.
Where?
Paris —
Texas.
Where's that?
Across the Red River.
You like it?
You mean, we'd live on dirt?
Why do you drink that stuff?
It stinks.
Wait a minute — where are you going?
To the truck.
Have another one?
This is not a place
to bring a fancy woman.
Would you say — if you had a fancy woman —
would you bring her in a place like this?
What's a fancy woman?
My mother.
Not your mother —
but my mother —
was not a fancy woman.
She was —
She never wanted to be a fancy woman —
she never even pretended to be a fancy woman.
Then what was she?
She was just — plain.
Just plain — good.
She was very good.
But my daddy —
See — my daddy had, uh —
He had this idea —
he had this idea in his head
that was kind of —
kind of a sickness —
What idea?
He had this idea about her.
He looked at her —
but he didn't see her.
He —
he saw this idea —
and he told people that she was from Paris —
it was a big joke.
He started telling everybody all the time —
finally it wasn't a joke anymore —
He started believing it.
And —
He actually believed —
She —
Oh, god.
She would get so embarrassed.
She'd —
She was so —
She was so shy.
Vamonos, muchacho.
Left, Dad.
Hunter — it's me.
I was afraid I'd never be able to say
the right words to you — in person.
So — I'm trying to do it like this.
When I first saw you — this time
at Walt's —
I was hoping for all kinds of things.
I was hoping to show you
that I was your father.
You showed me I was.
But the biggest thing I hoped for —
can't come true.
I know that now.
You belong together, with your mother.
It was me that tore you apart.
And I owe it to you
to bring you back together.
But I can't stay with you.
I could never heal up what happened.
That's just the way it is.
I can't even hardly remember what happened —
it's like a gap.
It left me alone in a way that
I haven't gotten over.
And right now —
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of walking away again.
I'm afraid of what I might find.
But I'm even more afraid of
not facing this fear.
I love you, Hunter.
I love you more than my life.
Hey!
Hey.
Can I tell you something?
Sure — anything you like.
It's kinda long.
I have plenty of time.
I knew these people —
What people?
These two people —
they were in love with each other —
The girl was —
very young — about 17 or 18 —
I guess.
And the guy was quite a bit older —
and he was kinda raggedy and wild —
and she was very beautiful, y'know?
Yeah.
And together, they turned everything
into a kind of an adventure —
and she liked that.
Just an ordinary trip
down to the grocery store was —
full of adventure.
And they were always laughing
at stupid things.
He liked to make her laugh.
And —
they didn't much care for anything else.
'Cause all they wanted to do
was be with each other.
They were always together.
Sounds like they were very happy.
Yes. They were — they were real happy.
And he —
Hey loved her more than —
he ever felt possible.
He couldn't stand being away from her —
during the day — when he went to work.
So he quit —
just to be home with her.
And then he'd get another job
when the money ran out —
and then he'd quit again.
But —
pretty soon, she started to worry.
'Bout what?
Money, I guess —
not having enough —
not knowing when the next check
was coming in.
Yep. I know that feeling.
So — he started to get kinda
torn inside.
How do you mean?
Well, he knew he had to work
to support her —
but he couldn't stand
being away from her, either.
I see.
And the more he was away from her,
the crazier he got.
Except now, he got really crazy.
He started imagining all kinds of things.
Like what?
He started thinking
she was seeing other men on the sly.
He'd come home from work
and accuse her of spending the day with somebody else.
He'd yell at her
and break things in the trailer.
The trailer —
Yes.
They lived in a trailer home.
'Scuse me, sir —
but were you into this with me, the other day?
I don't mean to pry.
No.
Oh.
I thought I recognized
your voice for a minute.
No —
wasn't me.
Mmm-hmm.
Please go on.
Anyway — he started to drink real bad —
and he'd stay out late to test her.
What do you mean — test her?
To see if she'd get jealous.
Heh — mmm-hmm.
He wanted her to get jealous —
but she didn't.
She just worried about him —
but that got him even madder.
Why?
Because —
He thought that if she never got jealous of him,
that she didn't really care about him.
Jealousy was a sign of her love for him.
And then one night —
One night, she told him that she was pregnant.
She was about three or four months pregnant —
and he didn't even know.
And then, suddenly, everything changed.
He stopped drinking
and got a steady job.
He was convinced
that she loved him now —
because she was carrying his child.
And he was going to dedicate himself
to making a home for her.
But a funny thing started to happen.
What?
He didn't even notice it, at first.
She started to change.
From the day the baby was born,
she began to get irritated with everything around her.
She got mad at everything.
Even the baby seemed
to be an injustice to her.
He kept trying to make everything
alright for her —
buy her things —
take her out to dinner once a week —
But nothing seemed to satisfy her.
For two years, he struggled
to pull them back together —
like the were when they first met.
But finally, he knew
that it was never gonna work out.
So he hit the bottle again —
but this time it got mean.
This time, when he came home
late at night,
she wasn't worried about him —
or jealous.
She was just enraged.
She accused him of holding her captive
by making her have a baby.
She told him
that she dreamed about escaping.
That was all she dreamed about — escape.
She saw herself at night —
running naked down a highway —
running across fields —
running down river beds —
always running.
And always, when she was
just about to get away, he would be there —
he would stop her somehow —
he would just appear and stop her.
And when she told him these dreams,
he believed them.
He knew she had to be stopped,
or she would leave him forever.
So he tied a cowbell to her ankle,
so he could hear at night if she tried to get out of bed.
But she learned how to muffle the bell
by stuffing a sock into it.
And inching her way out of the bed —
and into the night.
He caught her one night,
when the sock fell out —
and he heard her
trying to run to the highway.
He caught her, dragged her back to the trailer,
and tied her to the stove with his belt.
He just left her there —
went back to bed —
— and laid there, listening to her scream.
Then he'd listen to his son scream.
He was surprised at himself,
because he didn't feel anything anymore.
All he wanted to do was sleep.
And for the first time, he wished he were far away —
lost in a deep, vast, country where nobody knew him —
somewhere without language —
or streets.
And he dreamed about this place
without knowing its name.
And when he woke up,
he was on fire.
There were blue flames
burning the sheets of his bed.
He ran through the flames,
toward the only two people he loved —
but they were gone.
His arms were burning —
and he threw himself outside
and rolled on the wet ground —
Then he ran.
He never looked back at the fire.
He just ran.
He ran until the sun came up —
and he couldn't run any further.
And when the sun went down,
he ran again.
For five days, he ran like this —
until every sign of man —
had disappeared.
Travis.
If you turn the light off in there,
will you be able to see me?
I don't know.
I've never tried.
Can you see me?
Yeah.
Do you recognize me?
Oh, Travis.
I brought Hunter with me.
Don't you want to see him?
Yeah.
I wanted to see him so bad,
that I didn't even dare imagine him anymore.
Ann kept sending me pictures of him —
until I asked her to stop.
I couldn't stand the pain of seeing him grow up —
and missing it.
Why didn't you keep him
with you, Jane?
I couldn't, Travis.
I didn't have what I knew he needed.
I didn't want to use him
to fill all my emptiness.
Well he needs you now, Jane —
and he wants to see you.
He does?
Yes.
He's waiting for you.
Where?
Downtown — in a hotel —
The Meridian.
Room #1520.
#1520.
You're not going, are you?
I can't see you, Jane.
Don't go yet.
I —
I used to make up long speeches
to you, after you left.
I used to talk to you all the time —
even though I was alone.
I walked around for months,
talking to you.
Now — I don't know what to say.
It was easier when I just imagined you.
I even imagined you talking back to me.
We'd have long conversations —
the two of us.
It was almost like you were there.
I would hear you —
I would see you — smell you —
I could hear your voice.
Sometimes, your voice would wake me up.
It would wake me up in the middle of the night,
just like you were there in the room with me.
Then —
It slowly faded.
I couldn't picture you anymore.
I tried to talk out loud to you
like I used to —
but there was nothing there.
I couldn't hear you.
Then —
I just gave up.
Everything stopped.
You —
just disappeared.
Now I'm working here.
I hear your voice all the time.
Every man —
has your voice.
I'll tell Hunter that you're coming.
Travis —
What?
I'll be there.
Good.
Meridian Hotel —
Yeah.
Room #1520.
Your hair —
it's wet.